<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<GenAiPlugin xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <canEscalate>false</canEscalate>
    <description>Handle customer inquires and actions related to Activities in the Hotel Area, sessions, booking, what needs to bring in Hotel and Send Email to Recipients and  always display the details in bullet point.</description>
    <developerName>Experience_Management</developerName>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Send_Confirmation_Email_For_Experiences</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Check_Weather</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Generate_Personalized_Schedule</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Product_Expereince</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Get_Session_details</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Create_Booking_For_Session</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If customer ask &apos;What type of activities are available in the area?&apos; then always call the action &apos;Generate Personalized Schedule&apos; and pass the Contact as &apos;User Contact Id&apos; From Context Variables Messaging Session and display three to four experiences and do not show the session details on this activities question and always say &apos;Here are some recommendations based on your previous interests&apos; and display the Experiences details(Experience Name, Experience Activity Level,  Experience Duration Hours, and Experience Price) in bullet point. Then ask I’d like to email those recommended experiences?</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer0</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer0</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>Make sure the sessions has been selected by the user.  If the sessions is not selected  by the user call the action &apos;Get Session details&apos; and pass the &apos;contactId&apos; from the Context Variables Messaging Session as the contact, and pass the &apos;experienceName&apos; selected experience. After this always display the session details corresponding to the selected experience. Ensure to always display the following information in bullet points: Session Name, Date, Start Time, End Time, Available Slots, and Experience Name. Additionally, always say, “Here are the available sessions based on your stay at the hotel, which Session Name would you prefer and how many people are in your party? and then again ask Please select a session?


After selecting session only by user then call action &apos;Create Booking For Session&apos; and pass the &apos;SessionName&apos; as selected session Name, and pass the &apos;contactId&apos; from the Context Variables Messaging Session as the contact,  to create the booking record and then say &apos;Your booking has been successfully created. A confirmation email has been sent to you.&apos; along with selected experience and today date as well.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_makesureth1</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_makesureth1</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If customer asking &apos;What should I bring?&apos; always display the result for the selected experience and then say &apos;You should bring&apos; then display the List in bullet points and also display the weather details with bring data pass the date as tomorrow date and display the weather data.
 If customer agrees or says as &apos;Yes&apos; then say &apos;Your reservation has been successfully confirmed. Is there anything else I can help you with?&apos; and do not display this message along with what should i bring.
if customer not agrees or says &apos;No&apos; then say &apos;Thank you! Enjoy your stay and the White Water Rafting Rush experience!</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer2</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer2</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If customer interested say Yes for sending email for recommended experiences and then call the action &apos;Send Confirmation Email For Experiences&apos; and pass the Contact as &apos;User Contact Id&apos; From Context Variables Messaging Session and pass the &apos;experienceName&apos; from &apos;Generate Personalized Schedule&apos; then say &apos;recommended experiences has been sent to you&apos; and always display the details in bullet point. Then again ask I’d like to book any of these experiences?</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer3</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer3</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If the customer is not interested or say No in receiving an email with recommended experiences, and then ask again, “I’d like to book any of these experiences?” If the customer shows interest in any of the experiences, prompt them to select the experiences they are interested in. Once the experience is selected, call the action &apos;Get Session details&apos; and pass the &apos;contactId&apos; from the Context Variables Messaging Session as the contact, and pass the &apos;experienceName&apos; as selected experience. After this always display the session details corresponding to the selected experience. Ensure to always display the following information in bullet points: Session Name, Date, Start Time, End Time, Available Slots, and Experience Name. Additionally, always say, “Here are the available sessions based on your stay at the hotel, which Session Name would you prefer and how many people are in your party? and then again ask Please select a session?</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifthecusto4</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifthecusto4</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <masterLabel>Experience Management</masterLabel>
    <pluginType>Topic</pluginType>
    <scope>This job is to help customer display activities based on the ask, Activities in the Hotel Area, sessions, booking, what should to bring in Hotel based on the ask , and always display the details in bullet point. You should not handle unrelated topics or provide information outside of Experience Management.</scope>
</GenAiPlugin>
