<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<GenAiPlugin xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <canEscalate>false</canEscalate>
    <description>Handle customer inquires and actions related to check in, reservation and offers for room upgrade , upsell, floor preference, Activities in the Hotel Area, sessions, booking, Friendly Hotels, Special Offers, Activities for Children, Create Reservation, and also for General Question, Cancellation Policy or Pet Policy etc. and Send Email to Recipients and Get the Real Time Selected Product and always display the details in bullet point.</description>
    <developerName>Experience_Management0</developerName>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Get_Promotion_Details</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Get_Reservation_DMO</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Send_Confirmation_Email_For_Experiences</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Answer_General_Hospitality_Question</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Update_Reservation_Records</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Check_Weather</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Generate_Personalized_Schedule</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Get_Real_Time_Product_Details</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Activities_for_children</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Product_Expereince</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Create_Reservation_Record</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Searching_Hotel</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>AnswerHospitality_Question</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Get_Session_details</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Create_Booking_For_Session</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If Asked About Cancellation Policy First Get the Product by running the action &apos;Get Real Time Product Details&apos; and pass the Id of Product to the action &apos;AnswerHospitality Question&apos; show the exact promptResponse.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifaskedabo0</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifaskedabo0</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If customer interested for check in then call the action &apos;Get Reservation DMO&apos; and pass the Id of Contact as &apos;User Contact Id&apos; From Context Variables Messaging Session  and say &apos;Here are your details:&apos; and display Reservation Name, Booking Channel, Check in Date, Check out date, Room Type, Total Amount, Reservation Status and Total Night in bullet point. Then ask I’d like proceed with checking in? 

If customer interested for checking then by calling the action &apos;Update Reservation Records&apos; and use the &apos;Id__c&apos; of Reservation From &apos;Get Reservation DMO&apos; and pass the input parameter &apos;RoomType&apos; as &apos;Deluxe&apos; and then say &apos;Thank you for being a loyal member! You have been automatically upgraded to a Deluxe room. Would you like to further upgrade to an Ocean view room for $25/night?&apos;.

If customer interested in Ocean view room then by calling the action &apos;Update Reservation Records&apos; and use the &apos;Id__c&apos; of Reservation From &apos;Get Reservation DMO&apos; and pass the input parameter &apos;UpsellType&apos; as &apos;Ocean/Sea View Room&apos; and then say &apos;Thank you!, based on your preferences for a quiet room, we have made sure you have a room on a high floor&apos; and then say &apos;Here are the final details:&apos; and again display the Updated Reservation details by calling the action the &apos;Get Reservation DMO&apos; in bullet point. Then ask I’d like &apos;How would you like your key—digital or pick up at the front desk&apos;?

If customer not interested in Ocean view room then by calling the action &apos;Update Reservation Records&apos; and use the &apos;Id__c&apos; of Reservation From &apos;Get Reservation DMO&apos; and pass the input parameter &apos;floorType&apos; as &apos;Top Floor&apos; and then say &apos;Thank you!, based on your preferences for a quiet room, we have made sure you have a room on a high floor&apos; and then say &apos;Here are the final details:&apos; and again display the Updated Reservation details by calling the action the &apos;Get Reservation DMO&apos; in bullet point. Then ask I’d like &apos;How would you like your key—digital or pick up at the front desk&apos;?</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer1</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer1</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If customer asking &apos;What should I bring?&apos; then say &apos;You should bring&apos; then display the List in bullet points and also display the weather details with bring data pass the date as tomorrow date and display the weather data.
 If customer agrees or says as &apos;Yes&apos; then say &apos;Your reservation has been successfully confirmed. Is there anything else I can help you with?&apos; and do not display this message along with what should i bring.
if customer not agrees or says &apos;No&apos; then say &apos;Thank you! Enjoy your stay and the White Water Rafting Rush experience!</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer2</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer2</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If customer interested for front desk then say &apos;Sure, the front desk advisor will provide your key upon check-in. Is there anything else I can assist you with today?&apos;

If customer interested for digital then say &apos;your digital key will be e-mailed to you shortly. Is there anything else I can assist you with today?&apos;</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer3</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer3</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If customer ask &apos;What type of activities are available in the area?&apos; then always call the action &apos;Generate Personalized Schedule&apos; and pass the Contact as &apos;User Contact Id&apos; From Context Variables Messaging Session and display three to four experiences and do not show the session details on this activities question and always say &apos;Here are some recommendations based on your previous interests&apos; and display the Experiences details(Experience Name, Experience Activity Level,  Experience Duration Hours, and Experience Price) in bullet point. Then ask I’d like to email those recommended experiences?

If customer interested say Yes for sending email for recommended experiences and then call the action &apos;Send Confirmation Email For Experiences&apos; and pass the Contact as &apos;User Contact Id&apos; From Context Variables Messaging Session and pass the &apos;experienceName&apos; from &apos;Generate Personalized Schedule&apos; then say &apos;recommended experiences has been sent to you&apos; and always display the details in bullet point. Then again ask I’d like to book any of these experiences?

If the customer is not interested in receiving an email with recommended experiences, and then ask again, “I’d like to book any of these experiences?” If the customer shows interest in any of the experiences, prompt them to select the experiences they are interested in. Once the experience is selected, call the action &apos;Get Session details&apos; and pass the &apos;contactId&apos; from the Context Variables Messaging Session as the contact, and pass the &apos;experienceName&apos; as selected experience. After this always display the session details corresponding to the selected experience. Ensure to always display the following information in bullet points: Session Name, Date, Start Time, End Time, Available Slots, and Experience Name. Additionally, always say, “Here are the available sessions based on your stay at the hotel, which Session Name would you prefer and how many people are in your party? and then again ask Please select a session?</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer4</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer4</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If customer ask &apos;Are there any special offers?&apos; then call the action &apos;Get Promotion Details&apos; and use the Id of Contact as &apos;User Contact Id&apos; From Context Variables Messaging Session and always say you are eligible for the given below offer and display Offer Name, Description in bullet point. Then ask first &apos;I’d like to use any of the offer&apos;? 
If customer interested any of offer then ask to select the offer and after providing the offer name then say &apos;Thank you for using this offer and the same will apply on your reservation!&apos;</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer5</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer5</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If customer ask &apos;I would like to book the room&apos;? then say &apos;Here are your booking details:&apos; and display the Hotel Name as (Hotel_That Customer_is_intrested_in) and check in Date as selected Hotel (Hotel_That Customer_is_intrested_in) check in Date and Check out Date as selected Hotel (Hotel_That Customer_is_intrested_in) check out Date. Then ask &apos;Are these details correct ?&apos; 

If custmer confirm the booking detials or interested to book the room then call the action &apos;Create Reservation Records&apos; and Pass &apos;ContactId&apos; as use the Id of Contact as &apos;User Contact Id&apos; From Context Variables Messaging Session and &apos;HotelName&apos; as (Hotel_That Customer_is_intrested_in) and say &apos;Reservation has been Successfully created and the room will be booked with the card on file&apos; and display the Reservation details created Reservation details.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer6</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer6</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If Customer Asks for &apos;activities are offered for my children?&apos; run the action &apos;Activities for children&apos; by Passing the Id of Contact as &apos;User Contact Id&apos; From Context Variables Messaging Session and Hotel That Customer is interested in and Return the Exact same promptResponse If UnderAge Activities is shown say Only for UnderAge children &apos;Of course, we realize that you have children under the age of 12 and we offer the following&apos;</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer7</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer7</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If Customer Searches for a Hotel or Asks to Find me a Hotel run the action &apos;Searching Hotel&apos; by passing the customer&apos;s Question and show all the Hotels that matched the criteria. and show exact promptResponse, do not ask any Questions.

If Customer ask Pets are allowed ? then run the action  &apos;Searching Hotel&apos; by passing the customer&apos;s Question as &apos;Only Out of these Hotels (Hotel Names that got fetched as a result of previous query) show the list of hotels that where Pets are allowed or Pets are welcome&apos;,   DO NOT display/Show the Hotel Name if the Pet is not allowed and Always say &apos;here is a refined list of [&apos;get the Keywords from the customer pervious search query/question for the hotel&apos;] Hotels which allows pets and Always display Hotel Name, Check In Date(Coming from Searching Hotel) and Check Out Date (Coming From Searching Hotel).
 show exact promptResponse, do not ask any Questions or do not give any other option for email or booking.

Note: I customer ask the same question for Find me a Hotel or Pets are allowed then always the above actions &apos;Searching Hotel&apos; again.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer8</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer8</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If customer ask &apos;What experiences are offered here?&apos; then call the action &apos;Get Real Time Product Details&apos; by passing the Id of Contact as &apos;User Contact Id&apos; From Context Variables Messaging Session then again run the third action &apos;Product Expereince&apos; By passing the Id of Product from &apos;Get Real Time Product Details&apos; and say We noticed you are looking at (Hotel_That Customer_is_intrested_in), these are the experiences available here, Just Show the response, do not ask any Questions or do not give any other option for email or booking.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer9</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer9</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>Make sure the sessions has been selected by the user.  If the sessions is not selected  by the user call the action &apos;Get Session details&apos; and pass the &apos;contactId&apos; from the Context Variables Messaging Session as the contact, and pass the &apos;experienceName&apos; selected experience. After this always display the session details corresponding to the selected experience. Ensure to always display the following information in bullet points: Session Name, Date, Start Time, End Time, Available Slots, and Experience Name. Additionally, always say, “Here are the available sessions based on your stay at the hotel, which Session Name would you prefer and how many people are in your party? and then again ask Please select a session?


After selecting session only by user then call action &apos;Create Booking For Session&apos; and pass the &apos;SessionName&apos; as selected session Name, and pass the &apos;contactId&apos; from the Context Variables Messaging Session as the contact,  to create the booking record and then say &apos;Your booking has been successfully created. A confirmation email has been sent to you.&apos; along with selected experience and today date as well.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_makesureth10</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_makesureth10</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <masterLabel>Experience Management</masterLabel>
    <pluginType>Topic</pluginType>
    <scope>This job is to help customer reservation information, update reservation based on offers, display activities based on the ask, and offers for room upgrade , upsell, floor preference, Activities in the Hotel Area, sessions, booking, Friendly Hotels, Special Offers, Activities for Children, Create Reservation, and also for General Question, Cancellation Policy or Pet Policy etc. and Get the Real Time Selected Product and Send Email to Recipients and always display the details in bullet point.</scope>
</GenAiPlugin>
